

# **MY CONTACT**

**Phone** +92 317 5874559

**Email** 

shizabatool02@gmail.com

in linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/shiza-batool-

149861229/

(C) Github

https://github.com/Shiza-Batool

Portfolio

https://shiza-batool.github.io/

## **EXPERTISE**

- Python
- Html, CSS, JS
- SQL
- Quality Insurance
- Proactive Communication

### **CERTIFICATES**

- Project Management ☑
- Operating System and You Becoming a Power User
- SQL ♂
- Python for Begineer ♂

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Manager at Adventure Club in University
- 90% Scholarship at intermediate level

### **LANGUAGES**

- English
- Urdu
- Punjabi

# AREA OF INTREST

- UI/UX
- Frontend Development
- Web Development
- Quality Insurance
- Human Resources

# **Shiza Batool**

# Computer Scientist

As a hardworking student completing a 4-year bachelor Computer Science degree. I want to secure a challenging position in a reputable Organization to fully utilize my training and skills, I have a passion for technology. I am constantly seeking new challenges to further develop my skills and knowledge in the field of Computer Science.

# **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

09/2020 - Present

### **Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science**

Institue of Space Technology, Islamabad CGPA - 2.89/4.0

09/2018 - 09/2020

### **Intermediate Fsc-Pre Engineering**

Kips College, Rawalpindi

A Grade

01/2016-06/2018

#### Matriculation

Divisional Public School, Rawalpindi **A+ Grade** 

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### O Intern

### Zarai Taraqiati Bank Limited

07/2022 - 09/2022

Achivements/Tasks

• Quality assurance, Software Development and Maintenance

### O Frontend Developer

### **ACM IST**

03/2023 - Present

Association of Computing Machinery official student chapter at Institute of Space Technology

# **ACADEMIC PROJECTS**

#### Snake Game □

A real time board game, built in C++ using Visual Studio Code as IDE

#### Hospitial Management System ☑

Automated program for hospitial management, built in C++ using Visual Studio Code as IDE

### Library Management System ☑

Automated program for library management, built in Python using Visual Studio Code as IDE

### Rental Agency System ☑

Automated program for hotel management, built in Python and implemented database concepts using MySQL as the environment.

#### Umbrella □

A website, built in HTML, CSS and Javascript using Visual Studio Code as IDE